But it's kind of sudden
不过还真是突然呢
yes.
就是说啊
I don't know what kind of  reason it is.
也不晓得是吹什么风
In order to reward all of you for your active performance,
本部为了奖励你们的活跃表现
I can't believe that a two-day and one-night trip to the beach will as a gift.
竟然会送两天一夜的  海水浴场之旅当作礼物
Is it possible to say
难道说
while we are away…
他们打算趁我们不在时…
Give the Tya Tya to...
把茶茶小姐给…
No
不
Tya Tya will stay in the Saitama branch to be taken care of
茶茶小妹会留在埼玉支部接受照顾
You guys don't need to worry.
你们不需要担心
Yeah
这样啊
I'll take care of Tya Tya and Rumba
茶茶小妹和伦巴小弟交给我照顾
You should stretch and relax once in a while
你们偶尔也该伸展筋骨放松一下
sea
大海
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
Episode 9 "Golden Coast opening"
第九话「肌金海岸开放」
Then I'll pick you guys up again tomorrow
那我明天会再过来接你们
Until then, you guys have fun
在那之前你们先好好玩吧
Thank you, sir
谢谢你  叔叔
sea
大海
I didn't expect that there would be such a sand in the city.
没想到都内竟然有这样的沙滩呢
Golden Coast
「肌金海岸」
I've never been here before
以前从来没听过这里
But it seems to be a very famous tourist attraction
不过似乎是很有名的观光景点
and
而且
It is mentioned above that the first nude sand program in our country is being carried out here.
上面还说这里正在进行  国内首例的裸体沙滩化计划
I don't understand
什么跟什么啊
Then again
话说回来
There seem not to be any tourists here
这里好像完全没有游客呢
Great
很好啊
It feels like it's been wrapped up by us
感觉好像被我们包下来了
Good
好
The first person to enter the sea
第一个进到海里的人
can be added an extra course to dinner
晚餐可以多加一道菜
Accept the challenge
接受挑战
Wait a minute, Sora  Enjo Retto
等一下  宙  烈人
I'll lay the beach mat
沙滩垫我来铺就好
Hoshino, let's go and play together
星乃同学也一起过去玩吧
Well, I'm sorry
这样啊  不好意思了
You guys, well
妳们啊
Don't leave me on the sidelines.
不要把我晾在一旁啊
Hoshino is so unfrank
星乃同学就是这么不坦率
Well
对了
I have to wear sunscreen, too
我也得涂防晒乳才行
It's so comfortable
真舒服
This is my first visit to the seaside
这是我第一次来海边呢
What are you guys doing
妳们做什么啊
Now that we have come to play at the seaside
既然都来海边玩了
we should at least experience the salty taste of the sea
至少要体验一下海水的咸味呀
There seems to be something on my hand...
我的手上好像有什么…
What's that
那什么东西啦
What is this? Is it a sea cucumber
这是什么呢  是海参吗
I saw this breed for the first time
我第一次看到这个品种
How dare you touch that disgusting thing
真亏妳敢摸那种怪恶心的东西
It's not poisonous and harmful. Don't worry
它没有毒  没有危害性  放心吧
Really
是这样吗
How is that harmless
这样哪里无害了啊
That's strange
奇怪
This seems to be a very rare variety.
这好像是很罕见的品种呢
Come and help me
快来救救我
What's wrong with these guys
这些家伙是怎么回事
Is it just...
难道是刚才的…
Well, what on earth is that
真是的  那到底是什么东西啊
There's no way to enjoy a sea bath
这样根本没办法享受海水浴啊
Rarely come to the seaside
难得来到海边
But there is no way to play in the sea
却完全没办法进到大海里玩
sorry
不好意思
I'm going to go to the bathroom
我去上一下厕所
Well, we'll wait for you here first
那我们先在这等你吧
Sorry to keep you waiting
不好意思  让各位久等了
As I haven't had any guests for a long time
因为很久没有客人光顾了
it took me some time to prepare
所以花了一些时间做准备
No, it's all our fault
不  都要怪我们
Because we left the beach earlier than originally expected
因为离开海水浴场的时间  比原本预计的还早
That's why we came early. I'm sorry
所以我们才会提早过来  不好意思
Does it mean that the guests have entered the sea
难道说各位客人进到海里了吗
Then everyone must be surprised
那各位一定都大吃一惊吧
Right
是的
What on earth are those creatures
那些生物到底是什么
Think what you see is "iron cannon sea cucumber"
我想各位看到的恐怕是「铁炮海参」
Iron cannon sea cucumber
铁炮海参
Actually
这其实
It's the name given by our locals
是我们当地人取的名字
At the beginning of the year  a large number of new species of sea cucumbers began to appear
年初开始那种新种的海参  开始大量出现
No matter how much it is cleared, the number is still increasing
不管再怎么清除数量都还是不断增加
As a result, the number of tourists visiting the beach continues to decrease.
导致造访沙滩的游客不断减少
It's really nerve-racking
真伤脑筋
Although I am very sorry to you guests
虽然对各位客人很不好意思
Please give up the idea of playing in the sea this time
这次就请妳们放弃到海里玩的念头吧
That's too bad
真是糟糕
So bad that it's rare to have a chance to take a vacation
什么嘛  难得有机会渡假耶
Look at you
妳啊
We invited someone to expel sea cucumbers today
我们请人今天过来驱逐海参了
But they seem to be late
不过她们似乎是晚到了
Hello, we're here to expel sea cucumbers
妳好  我们来驱逐海参了
They seem to have just arrived
她们好像刚好到了
Wait for... What are you doing here
等…妳们怎么会在这里啊
That's what I'm going to say
这是我要说的话
Both of You calm down
妳们两个先冷静一点
What's going on
这是怎么回事
What a lovely cleaner
真是可爱的清理业者呢
Damn it
真是的
I don't know if you're here for a trip or something else
我不晓得妳们是来旅行还是干嘛的
But of course there's only one reason we're here
但我们来这里当然就只有一个理由啊
Let me see
我想想
Which way is the hall?
大厅是在哪个方向啊
sorry
不好意思
Excuse me, do you know where the men' toilet is
请问你知道男生厕所在哪吗
If you want to find the men's room, it's right over there.
要找男厕的话就在那边
Thanks
谢谢你
There are fewer tourists
游客少归少
There are people about our age
也是有和我们差不多年纪的人嘛
Excuse me
请问
Can it be said that you are Enjo Retto
难道说你是炎城烈人?
That's right
是这样没错
I'm a big fan of yours.
我是你的粉丝
Please shake my hand
请和我握个手吧
It seems too slow to speak after holding it
握完才讲好像太慢了
I'm fine
我是没关系啦
Don't you have to go to the bathroom
你不是要上厕所吗
Oh
对喔
Excuse me
我先失陪了
What's going on
怎么回事啊
I see
原来如此
Well
真是的
We're here to work, while you're here to play
我们来这里工作妳们却在这里玩
But there is such a coincidence in the world
不过天底下竟然有这么巧的事
Could this be part of my sir's plan
这会不会也是叔叔计划的一环呢
It's possible
有可能
So
所以
Didn't the Enjo Retto come here today
炎城烈人今天没有过来吗
So there is one person missing
这么说来确实还少一个人
Sure enough everyone is here
大家果然都在这里
What
什么嘛
It turns out that the two of them have already met
原来他们两个已经遇见了啊
Enjo
炎城同学
You guys... What are you doing here
妳们是…妳们怎么会在这里
What's the matter? Haven't you explained it to him yet
怎么了  你还没好好和他做说明吗
Sorry
抱歉
I've heard the rumors about you, Enjo Retto
我有听说过你的传闻  炎城烈人
I am Ginkgo
我是银杏木与那
For the time being, I am the leader of the Tokyo branch
姑且算是领导东京支部的人
The man who looks fragile is the Great River Orange Horse
这个看起来弱不禁风的人是大河橙马
Welcome your comments
请多指教
When those two men acted on their own a while ago
前阵子那两人自行行动时
It seems to have caused you trouble
好像给你们添麻烦了
I'm so sorry
真不好意思
Forget about that
那件事就算了啦
So, now that everyone's here
那么既然所有人都到齐了
Let's go, Saitama Branch
我们就出发吧  埼玉支部
How is it going, Moeno
怎么样  萌萎
Because the smell of the tide is not easy to tell
因为有海潮的气味不太容易确定
But there should be no Kisei Chuu around here
不过这附近应该没有规制虫
According to the locals
根据当地人的说法
When expelling sea cucumbers
之前在驱逐海参的时候
There have been several sightings of what appears to be a Kisei Chuu creature.
有好几个人目击疑似  规制虫的生物出没
There's nothing we can do
没办法了
We have no choice but to expel these guys before it comes out
在牠出没前只好先来驱逐这些家伙了
They say that Kisei Chuu... What on earth is going on
她们说规制虫…这到底是怎么回事
Well
这个嘛
According to the investigation of the Tokyo branch
根据东京支部的调查
There is Kisei Chuu lurking on this coast
有规制虫在这片海岸潜伏
And use those sea cucumbers to make the beach unusable
并利用那些海参使沙滩变得无法使用
Their battles really beat around the bush
她们的作战真的都很拐弯抹角耶
I heard the landlady say that just now
刚才听到老板娘那样说
We can't ignore it.
我们也没办法置之不理
That's why I decided to help now
所以现在才决定来帮忙
That's right
这样啊
So
所以
It is said that if you want to deport, how to do it in detail…
说要驱逐那具体上要怎么…
What are you doing
妳们在做什么啊
Do what? We're expelling sea cucumbers
做什么?  我们在驱逐海参啊
This kind of iron cannon sea cucumber will spray water to intimidate
这种铁炮海参会喷水进行威吓
But as long as a certain amount of water is spurted out
但只要喷出一定量的水分后
It will shrink and become unable to move
就会萎缩变得无法动弹
We need to rely on this battle to infuriate the Kisei Chuu
我们要靠这个作战激怒规制虫
To draw her out
好将她引出来
Then please help me, too
那么也请妳们一起帮忙吧
I didn't hear about this kind of help
我没听说要帮这种忙啊
Does Sora want to help, too
宙也要一起帮忙吗
I'm sorry. I won't hurt you
对不起  我不会弄痛你的
There's really nothing I can do about it
真是的  没办法了
What are we going to do
怎么办
It would be nice to let people who like to do that kind of thing
那种事让喜欢做的人去做就好了啦
Can't stand it
受不了
You guys are embarrassing HXEROS
妳们简直是在丢HXEROS的脸
I'm going to punish you for being so careless
做事这么不认真  我要好好处罚妳们
So... Then let's go over there and deal with it
那…那我们两个去那边处理吧
Just do it
就这么做吧
It's not Vladivostok. It's a sea cucumber worm
不是海参崴  是海参虫喔
It's nice to have Orange Horse here
有橙马在真是太好了
This male-to-female ratio is so strange
这个男女比例实在太奇怪了
It is often said that girls tend to feel more pleasure
常有人说女孩子感受到的快感  往往比较强烈
But is it okay for us to be so far away from everyone
不过我们离大家这么远没问题吗
Now, if there is a Kisei Chuu
现在要是有规制虫出现的话
it should be all right
应该没问题吧
Although it was not the original intention
虽然实在并非本意
But just now I have saved an H-Energy that Kisei Chuu shares.
但刚才我已经存到  一只规制虫份的H能源了
You're really good
你真的好厉害
Well, I have a favor to ask you
那个  我有一件事想拜托你
Please be my master
请你当我的师父吧
The reason why Cong Yu and Ruocao often act separately
丛雨同学和若草同学  之所以常分开行动
is because of me
可能就是我造成的
The source of my H-energy is a little strange
我的H能源的来源有点奇怪
Because it's hard to store energy
因为很难储存能源
So the mission always fails
所以任务老是失败
I've made trouble for the three of them several times
我已经给她们三人添过好几次麻烦了
But
但是
I heard that there are powerful heroes in Saitama who can sense H-Energy no matter what they do
我听说在埼玉有不管做什么  都能感应到H能源的强大英雄
So I have always admired Enjo
所以我一直很崇拜炎城同学
Is that a compliment
他这是在夸奖我吗
So if you have a knack for sensing H-energy
所以如果说你有感应H能源的诀窍
Please be sure to teach me
请务必教教我
You ask me the secret
你问我诀窍
I don't usually force myself to store it
我平常也没在勉强自己储存啊
Is it
是吗
I'm sorry to ask such a strange question
对不起  问了这种奇怪的问题
No
不
But I know how you feel as a boy trying to protect a member of the team
不过我很能了解你身为男孩子  想保护小队成员的心情
So as a HXEROS
所以同样身为HXEROS
I hope I can give you a hand
我希望能助你一臂之力
Really
真的吗
So before that  as your friend
所以在这之前  身为你的朋友
I want to know the H-energy source of Orange Horse first
我想先了解一下橙马的H能源来源
But it's embarrassing
可是这个很难为情耶
Don't be such an outsider
别这么见外嘛
It doesn't matter if we're all boys
我们都是男生又不会怎么样
It's actually
其实是…
The sound just now
刚才的声音
is from the girls
是女生那边传来的
This is...
这是…
Kisei Chuu
规制虫
Sea cucumber worm
海参虫
You deserve it  humans
这是你们是自作自受  人类们
How dare you treat my lovely pets
竟敢对我可爱的宠物们
in such an excessive way
做那么过分的事
Human H-energy is easy to accumulate in sensitive areas
人类的H能源容易蓄积在敏感的部位
How long can they hold out before H-energy dries up
在H能源枯竭前  她们还能再撑多久呢
I'm going to do what I did to other beach tourists
我要像对其他海滩游客做的那样
Squeeze out all your H energy
将妳们的H能源榨取殆尽
Damn it. It doesn't work at all...
可恶  完全使不上力…
Kirara
云母
Didn't you say you were sucked a little bit
妳不是说过自己被稍微吸一点
What's gonna happen
不会怎样的吗
That's what you say, but it's such a disgusting situation
话是这么说  可是这么恶心的情况
There is no way to feel H-energy at all
根本没办法感受到H能源啊
Orange Horse, come with me
橙马  你跟我来一下
I will attack the Noumenon of the Kisei Chuu later
我待会会先攻击规制虫的本体
The orange horse took advantage of this time    to take off the sea cucumbers on everyone
橙马趁这个时候  将大家身上的海参拿掉
I see
我知道了
That's weird
好奇怪
I obviously saw a picture like that
明明都看到那样的画面了
I have no sense of H-energy at all
我却完全感应不到H能源
Master  behind you
师父  你背后
It looks like there are humans hiding in other places
看来还有人类躲藏在其他地方
Come on and go away, damn it
快点走开  可恶
Are you all right
你没事吧
Barely
勉强可以
But
不过
My H-energy has almost been sucked away
我的H能源几乎都被吸走了
I'm afraid it's impossible to knock her down with one blow
这样要一击打倒她恐怕是不可能了
So orange horse
所以说橙马
It's up to you to save everyone
就由你来救大家吧
I can't do it
这种事我办不到的
Do you want us to help each other store H energy
难道你要我们两个  帮彼此储存H能源吧
This is really forcing people to do something difficult
这才真的是强人所难吧
That's right
是这样没错
Then I haven't finished what I just said
然后刚才的话我还没有说完
No matter what the source of your H energy is
不管你H能源的来源是什么
I wish I could help you
我都希望能协助你
Although the team they belong to is different
虽然所属的小队不一样
we're all partners. Aren't we
但我们都是同伴不是吗
Master
师父
You're right
说得没错
You can't hide like this all the time
也不能一直这样躲躲藏藏的
I can't believe he showed up on his own initiative
竟然自己主动现身了
You men have a lot of courage
你们这些人类真是有勇气呢
Orange horse
橙马
Is it really okay to give it to you
交给你真的没问题吗
Isn't that what you said?  Master
这不是师父你自己说的吗
Now it's up to me to store H-energy
现在也只能靠我储存H能源了
But you just didn't tell me. This is really...
但是你刚才什么也没和我说明  这样子实在…
Sorry
对不起
That's right
没错
My H-energy source
我的H能源来源
That's
那就是
Viewing H-Energy from the perspective of a third party
从第三者视角观看H能源
Wait... Where are your hands touching
等…你手在摸哪里啊
It was the Orange Horse who suddenly pushed me...
是橙马刚才突然推我…
Master's technique of receiving are really superb
师父的受身技巧真的好高超
To be able to land so accurately on a woman's body
居然能这么精准地  着陆在女人的身体上
See it with your own eyes like this
像这样子亲眼看
It feels far more exciting than watching a movie
感觉远比看影片还要刺激
There seems to be something inside me...
我的体内好像也有什么东西…
It's coming out
涌出来了!
Is it possible to say that   you are...
难道说  你们是…
The legendary... HXE... RO... S...
传说中的…HXE…RO…S…
I didn't expect that orange horse would defeat the Kisei Chuu  one day
没想到那个橙马  竟然有击败规制虫的一天呢
Everyone of the Saitama Branch
埼玉支部的各位
Thank you so much today
今天真的很谢谢妳们
It would be nice if I could give you some thank-you gifts
如果能给妳们一些谢礼就好了
Yu Na's personality is so serious
与那的个性就是这么认真
That's right
对了
Take it as a thank you  Would you like to come to Tokyo tomorrow
就当作是谢礼  各位明天要不要来东京玩呢
If you don't mind   I'll show you around
如果不嫌弃  就由我带妳们参观吧
Damn it
真是的
Why are you making your own decisions   Yu Na
妳干嘛擅作主张做决定啊  与那
Sorry
对不起
Is it true that Kusamura doesn't want to participate
丛雨同学是不是不想参加呢
If Enjo Retto will go
如果炎城烈人会去的话
Of course I'll be there
那我当然也会去啊
What a surprise
真是稀奇
Look  Sunset
妳们看  夕阳
Although a lot has happened today
今天虽然发生了很多事
But the thought of protecting the scenery
但一想到守护了这片景色
I think it's all worth it
就觉得都值得了呢
Are you all right  Master
你没事吧  师父
Do you have any abrasions on your body
你身上有没有擦伤
It's okay
还过得去啦
But thank you so much for today
不过今天真的很谢谢你
Thank you for listening to my request
谢谢你愿意听我的请求
Don't worry about this trifle
这点小事别放在心上
But I really envy you
但我真的很羡慕你
How do you exercise your body
你的身体是怎么锻炼出来的呢
I did do some retraining
我是有做点重训啦
I think it's better for Orange Horses to gain more weight
我倒觉得橙马应该  再多长一点肉比较好喔
Orange horse
橙马
I don't think there's anything else you're not telling me
你应该没有其他什么事瞒着我吧
No
没有啊
Yeah, that's good
是这样就好
Sorry
对不起
My nipples are a little bigger than the others
我的乳头比其他人还要大一点
So I feel very embarrassed
所以觉得很难为情
Never mind
别在意
I just feel like it's weird to have a crotch
就觉得怎么胯下好像怪怪的
Was the sea cucumber glued to the body just now
原来是刚才的海参黏在身上吗
You should have noticed earlier
你也该早点注意到吧
Scared me
吓我一跳
The skin is really exposed too much
真是的  肌肤部分也露太多了吧
I can't watch it anymore. help him put it back on, okay
都看不下去了  帮他重新穿好吧
It's dawn
天亮啰
Are you all up, boys
你们都起床了吗  男生们
You don't have to shout so loud and we can hear you
不必喊得那么大声也听得见啦
Are you so dissatisfied with your desires  Retto
难道你就这么欲求不满吗  烈人
I'm sorry. I didn't even notice
对不起我都没有注意到
What's going on
搞什么嘛
If you said to me earlier
早点和我说的话
I can help you, too
我也可以一起帮你的啊
That's not like that
不是这样
That's right
果然没错
Help me  Orange Horse
快救救我  橙马
Good morning  Master
早安  师父
Thank you so much
真是太感谢各位了
Today, my son heard that the sea cucumbers on the coast had disappeared
今天外子听说海岸的海参消失了
We are so excited
兴奋得不得了呢
Thanks to all of you, this is finally saved
托各位的福  这下终于得救了
We provide free meals in the morning
早上的餐点是我们免费提供的
Please enjoy it
请各位尽情享用吧
So
所以说
Are they going to take us to Tokyo for sightseeing later
待会她们要带我们去东京观光吗
I don't know where it will take us to visit
不晓得会带我们去什么地方参观呢
Well
这个嘛
I'd like to consult you guys first
我想先征询一下大家的意见
I want to go to a place where I can heal my body and mind
我想去能疗愈身心的地方
I want to see if there are any new heroes around
我想找找看有没有最新的英雄周边
I hope to see the food attractions... Kind of like that
我希望能去看看美食景点…之类的
Is there really such a perfect place
真有这么刚好的地方吗
In that case
既然这样
I see
原来如此
That place should be very suitable
那个地方应该非常适合
Is it
是吗
The kids in the Tokyo branch...
东京支部的那些孩子们…
I was just about to pick them up
我才正准备要过去接他们的
Never mind
没关系
Well, be careful on that road
那路上小心
In that case, I'll get some sleep first
既然这样我就先睡个觉吧
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
Next time, "two Kirara"
下一回「两个云母」